Fish oil! Oh my, what should I do?
Dad, I'm fucked
Woosungah
What does that mean?
Oh, I don't know, I guess I hit someone.
Please do something quickly!
No, no, Charlotte!
119, right?
The kid got hit, please come quickly.
What should I do!
No, please...
please
Please help!
Uh, sit down.
What is it? What kind of emergency is this?
Have you come this far? huh?
You know Rep. Kwon’s son, right? Woosung
Uh, that...
It's time for him to be discharged from the military.
As soon as it comes out today
I hit someone while drinking.
That's why
This is Sullivan's daughter.
Oh my
Are you hurt a lot?
There hasn't been an official announcement yet.
at the hospital
They say it's hopeless
Did you kill someone while drinking?
Rep. Kwon
Did you know that he is the next Speaker of the National Assembly?
If Rep. Kwon saves Woo-seong,
They say Kiyun City’s IT special zone will help.
Is there any way?
Yes
Are there any?
If I am discharged today, I am still a soldier.
I was on a mission then
Trials are also held in the military.
Then he lives
Oh, by the way
But I guess the appeal will be filed outside again.
I'll take care of it then.
yes
But the Minister and Sullivan
Are you not a business partner?
Ah, indeed
We need to distinguish between public and private matters.
Sullivan is a ball
The next Speaker of the National Assembly is
Huh?
Oh no
Why?
Brother
It's Sullivan.
What?
us bomb in arab
The guy who paid twice as much for it
What?
That person
The Minister of Defense?
Yes
Well, then we
They caught the Minister of National Defense.
What I said back then is correct.
No, what the hell
How dirty is the back?
Capturing civilians?
Still, that's pretty much it.
It will clank clank, right?
Well, I'm glad then
Wow, like this
I didn't know he was a high person.
Are you still bugged?
It's disconnected
I think I found it over there.
I'll upload that video
To the Vice Minister first
I'll report it to you
I'll pass it on
I have something to talk about when we meet
yes
Those children
How do you know this place?
I guess
I think my location has been tracked.
There was also something like this on the wall.
What is this?
Are you bugged?
What's missing?
Well, that...
What!
I ripped off all the buttons on my clothes.
However, a button?
Well...
What, something like this?
how
take the kids
Will we catch them all?
Man
There was too much exposure.
Clean up the residue and empty this place.
I need to know what they took
I'm not going to deal with it and move on.
You, you bastard, have...
Oh, just leave your head alone, Mr.
So should we just leave it alone?
Who leaves it alone?
You can't leave it alone
You worked hard
We'll start investigating right away.
It was the minister who brought PD Kim with him.
You really didn't know?
Or you knew it all from the beginning
Did you approach me on purpose?
It may be related to corruption in the defense industry.
Well, I had my doubts
I didn't know they were kidnapping civilians.
That defense industry corruption
A bomb exploded in our neighborhood
Are they related?
We're looking into that.
If you're using me...
There is no such thing
I'll hand this over to my department.
I'll contact you when something comes up.
honey
Oh, it's okay
What about Doyeon?
Until dad comes
I held on to wait
I fell asleep a little while ago
What I went to
Did you solve it well?
Here's how it happened...
Oh, that's it.
Anything is good
Don't make it difficult for me and Doyeon.
Got it?
yes
Uh, right
I was coming home with Doyeon earlier.
Who did you meet?
sullivan
Who?
james sullivan
At the amusement park before
The person who gave Doyeon ice cream
I guess it's Sullivan
Didn't you say anything?
Yeah
I said hello to Doyeon and left.
All over the neighborhood
I think I'm going to see it
Why?
Uh, ah, no.
Let's go in
Yeah
I can't connect
Connected to voicemail...
Ana, you son of a bitch.
This thing keeps chewing up the phone
uh
Minister
Let's go together
Those involved with bombs
Something related to bombs
I told you not to leave everything behind.
sorry
I will handle it
What, what do you handle?
uh?
What
What are you going to do?
This is ridiculous
with manipulated video
You guys
Do you doubt me?
Did you fact check this?
I need to be sure about this
You and me
One of them will die
Do you know?
It's a procedural investigation.
To return to work
You need to explain
A calling! Mr.
What is there to call?
I didn't do anything wrong
Let's go out
Who are you dating?
Are you trying to soak me?
What are you saying?
Or
Where did you get that?
I was reported
I can't reveal who it is
Oh my
Those bastards
I was wondering who I could trust and who I was fooling around with.
So, it was you?
Come to work
Okay
Oh my, you frustrating person.
you now
Do you know what you're doing?
These are the guys from whom I stole bombs.
The board was laid out to catch it.
He's ruining everything now.
think about it
Minister of National Defense of the Republic of Korea
I barely managed to steal a few bombs.
Would you commit corruption?
Kid...
- Bye, bye
- Hello!
- I'll go, okay.
- Hello
- See you later.
- Uh
we
I'm going to make it like that
I'm going to draw a sketch first.
This is Pinky
Ouch
Brother!
uh
Ah, hey, it's been a few days.
Does it still hurt?
- Oh, it's okay.
-Sleep.
here, there, pasrang
I also bought painkillers and anti-inflammatory medication.
- Hey, thanks.
- Yes
To them, huh?
It was just a one-sided beating.
That's right, Sasha
I come in with a sense of tact.
While avoiding it
Shock...
Oh my
Brother, hey, first of all
You have to attach this cool patch first.
Uh, okay
And brother
Please give me a stamp, okay?
- uh?
- Don't just avoid it, grab it.
Just grab it and hand it over.
Special attack! Hey!
And kicking, yay!
- With the basics like this
- Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my
No, it's been a few days
Isn't there a line in the article?
Uh, this is with Changri Church.
Hi Apartment Senior Citizens’ Center
- Uh
-There's a receipt inside.
Honey, how is your back?
What's wrong with my back?
Ah, these past few days
I groaned all night while I was sleeping
Where have you been and what have you been doing, really?
This pretty face too
I just scratched it here and there, really.
Ah, I was just taking things down.
I heard it was a bit like that
You want me to believe that now?
I went to the warehouse and it was very clean.
Did you organize it?
Oh, since the goods arrived yesterday
I just cleaned it up
Not so good?
One hand is rough
as much as you
Because no one is meticulous
As expected, our goddess Jeong Nam-yeon
If you admit it
Well, that’s Jjin, Jjin!
I'll go to the delivery and come back
Wow
Ah, waist...
Oh my
Hey
Hey, it's coming down there.
It's Thursday Man, right?
That's right
The Man of the Second Thursday
Let's work
- Let's go, let's go, let's go
- Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go
Huh? That one
It's a bus going to my neighborhood.
There are a lot of alleys in that neighborhood.
Perfect for lying down
So is that day today?
maybe?
♪ Recognition ♪
♪ Rururu lalili rururu la ♪
♪ Tooru lariru too ♪
Oh no, no, no
Oh my!
ah!
Hey, are you okay?
- Uh-uh, don't touch it.
- Uh, okay, I won't touch it.
Oh my, I'm dying
Well, just wait a moment.
I'll call 119
- 119 What number is it?
- Ah, us.
Wow, he passed away
I see my mom and dad
Oh my dad
Yes, yes, hello
Me, me, me...
yes, it's okay
It's a river
Brother, I will handle it.
Well...
You can wake up now.
Who are you?
Don't you remember me?
I've seen it before
right away
You were driving below the speed limit, right?
Yes, probably.
That's an alley
Ha, is it 30 or 50?
How do you know?
I
How loud was the sound of being hit by a car?
Oh, and
Oh, there's no CCTV here!
ah! Wow, my waist
Ah! Wow, ribs
Oh, I don't know, I don't know
Please call 119
I need to do you a favor.
Oh my, oh my
Now
Look, look
speed 24km
This is road 30
Oh! It says 30 right there!
And you were the one responsible for speeding.
I bounced too far
Teacher, why is it always only Thursday?
Do you have accidents? uh?
We also have a lot of work on Thursday.
Ah, what do you mean?
I got hit by a car and now I
Dead life, now!
We
Even before the accident
The teacher was filming everything.
With this
This is what I only heard
insurance fraud
It's insurance fraud, right?
- Wow, really.
- Oh my, that's right.
Wow, teacher
By deliberately causing accidents like this,
If you get insurance money
Imprisonment of up to 5 years or
The fine is less than 20 million won.
When the Special Act on Prevention of Insurance Fraud is applied
Is that strong?
Imprisonment of up to 10 years or
Up to a fine of up to 50 million won
I know you guys are lucky.
- Huh?
- Look, hey, just walk.
Teacher, where are you going?
- He's running, now he's running.
- Ana...
Wow, it came just in time.
Huh?
Jeonghwan is here?
Wow, the engine is making noise.
He's a fun person
It's funny, I also
Brother, I'm here
What, where are you two going?
I met you on the way
Oh, really?
I'm going in
Let's go together
How is there not a single article?
I knew it would be like this
hello
Ms. Sujin
Have you heard from the Vice Minister?
Oh yeah, not there yet
Ms. Sujin
Jeonghwan, why did you come?
Oh, me too
I came here to hear some news.
Not there yet
Brother, but I’m still in pain here.
Is it always like this?
Your tenacity is terrible, and you are young.
do some exercise
Ah, among the mercenaries.
There are many former special forces
If you hit it wrong, it goes to goal.
Right?
Hey, Sujin.
Why do you keep taking Junghwan’s side?
Have you ever taken sides?
I've never taken your side
Okay
Um, PD, have you eaten?
I brought you something delicious
Ah...
What is it? Oh, that sounds delicious.
There are a lot of them
Let's eat together
I ate
Please go to the bathroom
Oh, I ate a lot earlier too.
Oh, what is it?
Did you two eat together?
Oh, give me that, give me that.
don't eat
I have to bring it back.
Ah, so what is the standard?
What should I report?
Is there more compensation?
Shouldn't you write it down?
Oh, are you here?
W sit down, uh
Wow, it smells like paste
Is it a lot?
It doesn't fly much
What, have you plastered everything on your body?
How many did you add?
How many, three?
Oh my, really
Ugh, is it because I’m older?
It lasts quite a long time
Are you okay where you got hit?
I
look here
I put a paste on it that doesn't smell.
- Oh my, oh my
- Hey, my goodness.
I'm proud
By the way, is Doyeon’s dad okay?
He's okay
You saw it, bam bam
yes
Please take good care of me by my side
Well, the two of them got along really well.
Hey, by the way, huh?
When did you send the video?
Well, the minister appears in the news.
Or give us compensation
What should I do?
So, I came here because I was frustrated too.
Did you hear anything from Doyeon’s dad?
500 won if you’re curious
Oh, just give me 300 won.
Ah! No, no
None, none, none
IC
goodbye
Catch Thursday's Man too, huh?
Save the neighborhood brother too, huh?
I also pulled out the team leader’s sick tooth.
Iltasampi!
I am this kind of person
This Vertigo ace! uh?
- Deputy Director Kim
- Yes
Good job
Oh no
Team leader, why is it only Deputy Director Kim and me?
with your mouth
You just said all of the common phrases, just now.
How can you not give yourself a chance to praise? uh?
It's Chisa Pantsu, it's Chisa Pantsu.
Deputy Director Kim
Because I was the one who looked at the shoes.
The report was written by Deputy Director Kim.
I'm still writing it
I wrote seven out of ten, so why bother?
Yes, PD Kim
I already tried to contact you
Okay, I'm going now.
Where are you going?
I need to meet someone
I'll go to work outside and leave from there.
Deputy Director Kim, thank you for your hard work today.
Well then, team leader, see you tomorrow.
Ah, this guy, is it natural?
Oh, I also work outside...
- sit down
- Yes
Are you alone?
yes
Sujin went out for a moment.
What did you want to meet for?
Minister Kim Seok-jun
for a few days
I kept researching
There is no content at all in the chirashi.
I find that strange too.
Let alone a minister
There is no news about corruption in the defense industry.
In the case of such a high person
It's either
Explode or explode
buried or
When I was at the broadcasting station before
I've covered something like this a few times.
Just get everyone killed
I quit because I was so angry.
PD
Let’s upload a video of Seokjun Kim.
This is what I hoped for
If you post a video, there will be a reaction, right?
Well, I guess it will squirm.
uh
What?
Why is Lee Geun-cheol going there?
I am the minister
Hey!
Until the end of the internal investigation or investigation,
I am the minister!
Hey, huh?
Ouch! Mr.
Ana, how dare these things attack me?
Uh, where are you now?
Why do you keep following me?
You’ve come to my house before, right?
I'm going to report you guys.
Let go, let go of this!
hey!
Ugh!
Oh no, Mr!
are you okay?
yes, it's okay
- What about your sister?
- Uh, I'm fine.
Lady, they came all the way here.
Doyeon
What if we go to Doyeon?
- Where are you now?
- Kindergarten.
Just stay still
Then Yonghee is faster
Yes, I'm waiting now
They said the teacher brought them out.
Doyeon
Yonghee is bringing me now.
yes
But
Are you okay?
Ah
Oh, this?
Hey, I was unloading here.
I'm a little hurt, uh
Ah, but by the way
Where did those guys come from?
I didn't know when I got off the bus.
As I was walking, I saw him next to you.
I followed you a few days ago too.
Then I couldn't see it
I thought maybe I was being sensitive.
Did you talk to Doyeon’s dad?
no
Oh, then hurry...
Just stay still
Hey mammoth
Where are you? uh?
- Wait a minute.
- Hey
uh
Hey, when Yonghee comes later
Going into Doyeon’s mom’s house
Go check it out
Hey, what about Kang?
I don’t think Doyeon’s father knows yet.
you stay here for a moment
I feel like these are messing with my family
I'm going to go see Minseo.
Uh, Minseo, hey, go quickly.
Mr. Jesu, you were very surprised, right?
Ah, that
This is Kwak Byeong-nam, the youth president.
Ah, yes
I heard a lot of words
What happened to the face...
Oh, this?
While feeding a stray cat
There was a fierce guy
They only give me food
Suddenly, 'Kyeah!' And then it just clicked...
yes
Oh, did you contact Kang?
I tried it, but it doesn't connect.
Are you busy?
Baby, don't worry
There are all the people in the neighborhood, so what?
yes
- Did you guys watch a porn video yesterday?
- I saw it.
Isn’t he really handsome?
But it's not my style
What are you talking about?
I like men best
Why is it like that?
- It's a man.
- I have to go there.
- Oh, bye.
- Hello, bye bye.
Huh?
Mom, why are you here?
uh
Here, uh, around here
I have some business to do.
looking at you
I just ran, now, uh
Hey Minseo, today is just
let's just go home
take a break from academy
Just get tutoring at home
Oh, wow, what a win.
Oh my...
yes
dog gain
Uh, it's me
Why can't I contact you?
Oh, I'm in a meeting.
I'm going now, why, what's going on?
what?
Are you coming now?
What happened?
Oh, well
Those kids are in town again
This is why finishing is important
So what, how
What, kill them all?
If necessary
You are not JDD anymore
I just have a wife and a daughter.
He's a neighborhood guy.
So my family
I'm not saying I'm going to protect it.
By killing people?
Earlier, the mammoth saved Mr. Jesu.
Yonghee was brought by Doyeon.
Take me home together
You touched the baton with me a little while ago.
We can protect it together
So you
Don't even think about crossing the line
Huh?
If you cross the line to protect two people
Someday Doyeon
You'll avoid it, man
Going
Oh my, this is frustrating.
Brother, take his words to heart.
Are you okay?
What about Doyeon?
I fell asleep while reading a book
Come see me
Mikyungah
Why didn't you answer the phone earlier?
I'm sorry
I went to meet someone
The phone wasn't working there.
sit down
In this neighborhood
What is going on?
mammoth boss
The face that was normal at Changri Market
Everything is broken...
The youth president's face is also a mess.
Don't use your head
Tell me straight from the beginning
When I moved here
I went to throw away the trash
You got hurt when the ATM exploded.
Actually at that time
A bomb had exploded
I am Inseop Kim
I told you to get rid of it!
Are you guys going to do your work like this?
Bomb related niggas, bomb related
I told you not to leave everything behind.
Hey, PD Kim
Well, what if I post it without saying anything?
inside
You said you were investigating.
SNS, gossip, news
I have nothing to do with it anywhere.
I can't even use this in trial.
illegal evidence
They were pretending to investigate that.
Oh no, it's going to be a blur.
I did this kind of research
I know it well because I have done it a lot.
Still
There should have been at least some consultation.
Then just time passes
Oh, what are they doing now?
I might be planning it.
What are you doing?
If you upload a video without consulting
That's what I'm going to say
Those guys in broad daylight
tried to kidnap my wife
And that too in the middle of the neighborhood
What?
Ordinary local people
It seems like you don't even care
If you're originally high up
It's hard to see things like that.
uh
Let's take a look
Where?
Ah, yes, yes, yes
See you there, yeah
Turn the car around
Hey
Hey, you, Mr.
It's going to come down anyway...
Huh?
Oh, why don’t you come up, Mr.
Hey, after all, soldiers are different.
You have good physical strength.
Did you see the video?
The Minister was fucked
I'm not in the mood to mess around right now
I'm not kidding either.
Minister, it was a close call.
Ouch!
take a breath
Here, the air is good here
When you breathe clean air
I'm just bursting with ideas
Oh, I'm dizzy
Did you find the guy who set off the bomb?
sullivan
IT Special Zone That Sullivan
You're a bold bastard
Right? Ganddaega
Because I came out of the boat
Our stuff, that bastard
He said he bought it at twice the price.
What should I do with this?
Minister, how much do you trust me?
huh?
many?
No, I told you so.
We were on the same boat
Prepare a bomb
Let me blow it up
What?
yes
Okay, okay, uh
Oh, okay, huh?
Wow!
Ki, bursting into kiyun poetry?
Take a hit at the police box
There is symbolism.
A symbol of public power and public safety
Why?
Sullivan took revenge
This is what I did
If you say that reporter is also part of the gang.
Will public opinion remain silent?
At that time, the minister came forward
I was trying to catch a terrorist.
That's it.
Oh, Mr.
Oh, he's so creative.
He...
Wow, I need to learn something like that.
Oh my, lady
Wow
Seokjun Kim
You're as tall as me
Wow!
sullivan
How dare you me
Check your liver?
Let's send them both away at this point, okay?
Does this make sense?
Butane gas bought at a convenience store
It explodes and someone dies...
sorry
I will handle it
What, what do you handle?
uh?
What are you going to do?
shaking
That there is
Accordingly, I contacted the butane gas manufacturer.
make a strong protest
The previous government is here
I once again strongly condemn
Wow!
Hey, who can see this?
It's Namyeon Jeong, this is it, huh?
Ha, somehow
Somehow
I get it now, now, ah...
It's so cool, really
Oh, what is it?
Why is this happening all of a sudden?
Oh, stay still, stay still
Have you had a hard time so far? huh?
To protect the neighborhood
I'm hurt and suffering alone
What, Dan, how did you know?
I'm your husband, don't you know that?
You know it when you see it
Namyeon Jeong
I'm behind you
Don't worry
Do big things
It's cool
what?
Did Byeongnam talk about it?
Mr.
True
Wow, that's amazing.
It's like a real movie
Oh, this is the real Namyeon?
Yeah, you know bro
Our Namyeon
707 Former instructor
A while ago that
You even dismantled the bomb.
Uh, right
Wow, still true
True
No, at the entrance to this town
There's a gas station.
- Yes
- According to my intuition
There was some sort of strategy meeting there.
I think I do, huh?
It's far away
It's hard to see so
child
That's not the gas station building.
That basement
Basement?
Ah, why, when it was first built there
I want to dig the ground so deep
Did you make an oil storage tank?
They built something like a bomb shelter.
Room...
Oh, why, you know
Hey, if something like war happens
Where people hide
Ah!
ah! That...
Oh, that's why everyone didn't see it.
So...
Ah!
Minseo
Teacher!
Teacher, why did you come here?
uh? Teacher, what’s wrong with your face?
Did you fight with my mom?
My mom’s face was hurt too.
Me and my mother?
I just came to pick you up
Huh?
There's a lot of tutoring time left.
Didn’t your mother tell you?
For the time being, teacher
I'll keep coming to get you
let's go
Awesome, why?
Because I can go to class quickly
So what about days without tutoring?
Even if you’re not there, I’ll come get you, hurry and get in.
- Fasten your seat belt
- Yes
Anything is good
Don't make it difficult for me and Doyeon.
Got it?
We can protect it together
So don't even think about crossing the line
If you cross the line to protect two people
Someday Doyeon
You'll avoid it, man
yes
I just brought it to you.
Until your brother or sister-in-law comes
Because it will be in our dojo
Don't worry, come slowly.
thank you
Director!
let's play together
Uh, I'll go.
See you later, brother.
Minseo, go in first.
I'll park and go
yes
This is Sujin Lee
Mr. Jeonghwan
Yes? A mercenary?
Wait a minute, can I...
Hey, what is a mercenary? say it again
Again?
These kids
Why are you coming to someone else's neighborhood?
I'm following along now.
Uh, let me contact you.
What is it?
They said they showed up again
I think it's because of the video I uploaded.
No, no, no
Oh, it won't explode here, Mr.
I'll go
- Uh
- Uh, hey.
Hey, they say they're in our neighborhood again
Where are you?
now
Jeonghwan is chasing after me
I'll be there in 20 minutes too
Share your location with me too
Don't kill me, okay?
Yeah, man, that
If you listen to adults
Because rice cakes form even while you sleep...
Hey, Mr. Lee, with his temper, Mr.
uh
The police box side?
Hey, there's CCTV there.
Uh, hang up.
- I came.
- Are you here?
child
I can go get it
Now
Hey, I'm having a hard time all the time.
You can get this level of service
- Thanks, yes.
- Oh, good job.
Oh, that's right, that, that, that...
Did you see that?
What?
Oh, that, that
That one that was posted on you tube
"Nobus"
Uh, Soo-il hyung.
AC
Uh, bastard
Uh, bro
Is there a box in front of the police box?
What, a box?
box...
uh
Uh, there, there is
Should I give this to Police Officer Park?
No, no, don't go in.
open it
uh
Wait a minute, but I'm here
How did you know?
Oh, open it.
Mistaking other people's things?
You don’t like it?
Oh, brother, please
Well, open it!
Wow, it’s really tinkling.
Okay, okay.
What is this, this?
uh? What is this...
Inside...
Oh, wait a minute.
Hey, hey, sick boy, hey
This is a gun, gun, bomb, bomb.
Hey, what should I do about this?
Brother, listen to me carefully.
Leave it as is
Get in the car fast, go as far as you can
Uh, okay
Hey, sleep, wait a minute.
Oh, there's Policeman Park in there too...
So, to Police Officer Park
Tell me to run away quickly
Okay, okay, just hang up for now.
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Wait a minute
i am now
Because I'm heading towards Hanbalsan Mountain.
- Follow carefully.
- Yes
I'm on a suburban road right now.
Huh?
Hey, step on it
Brother, what are you doing?
Ah, brother, run away quickly!
If it explodes here, it explodes
I don't think it will work
Mr. Lee
Brother
Soo-il, are you crazy? Mr.
Brother, what's wrong?
Hey, you go down quickly.
Finding mammoth car through CCTV
- Yes, yes
- quickly, quickly
Uh, uh
Brother, can you hear me?
What should I do?
I don't know
But this is in the middle of the neighborhood
It shouldn't explode
How long is the sea from here?
Ah, you never know when it might explode.
It's too far away!
Stop this for now
Let me say goodbye to Namyeon.
Soo-il, brother!
AC
Ah...
Uh, why aren't you calling?
Uh, uh, Namyeon
Why, again, what?
No, you know
I'm with Minseo
There's only you
You know?
what's the matter? Soo-il Kim
Where are you hurt?
I am Kim Soo-il.
Jeong, Namyeon Jeong, only you
loved
What's going on?
IC
This is Mr.
When I speak like the main character
Put down the tin, Mr.
Why, why!
Brother
Come to the gas station
You crazy man, now with the bomb
Are you going to the gas station?
Listen to me and come to the gas station
How long does it take?
"Run remote connection"
No way
“Detonation signal transmission completed”
Hey, hey, why...
Sister
Stop it now!
You saved the world!
- Yeah.
- I saved the world
If it weren't for my brother
It almost caused a real mess.
IC
This is Mr.
When I speak like the main character
Put down the tin, Mr.
Why, why!
Brother
Come to the gas station
You crazy man, now you have a bomb
Are you going to the gas station?
Listen to me and come to the gas station
How long does it take?
One or two minutes?
So, so, so fast?
Hey, I'm Kim Soo-il.
Just wait
I almost got in big trouble
Brother
You saved the world, sister.
Oh, that's because I'm worried.
Mr. Inseop Kim
I'm moving to another safe house today.
Oh, where?
I can't tell you where
It'll be safer than here.
yes
Hey, really
Brother, you did so well, you did so well
The counter-terrorism team is coming.
Oh, really?
No, but how can I do this?
Thinking of bringing it here...
Ah, here
Radio waves are blocked, yes.
What if it's a time bomb?
Oh, sure, brother.
Hey, I
I checked first to see if there was a timer.
Am I stupid?
One way or another
Than something that explodes in the neighborhood
- Better blow up here, right?
- That's right, good job, bro.
My stomach almost exploded, really.
- Stop hitting me.
- Stop it now, it hurts too much.
Really now
Stop it, stop it
What are you? Just do this
Hey, here by the way
Hey, what is it?
uh? cool
Wait a minute, you too
Hey, it's like some kind of commando, huh?
Our local special forces
unsophisticatedly
What is it other than ‘Five Eagle Brothers’?
Why, bro, you’re cool
It's okay
What is it to our Soo-il...
No, I just think
I think it's a bit old-fashioned
That's it
Your clothes are the most boring
Ugh, Mr.
Where are you going?
Did you order Mi-kyung to be kidnapped?
What bullshit is that!
Don't make me say the same thing twice
You
He's the strongest, right?
What are you doing you bastard?
I ask the questions
you are my wife
Did you order me to kidnap you?
yes, i did it
Why?
I ordered it to catch you
Who set off the bomb in Changni-dong?
What do you do with that?
You said you never said the same thing twice
Sullivan! Sullivan!
Sullivan, Sulli...
J, James, James Sullivan
Sir, Sullivan...
I also confirmed that the bomb was stolen.
It's dangerous!
Our Myung-oh...
What is that ice cream?
That guy
gave me ice cream
I was coming home with Doyeon earlier.
Who did you meet?
Sullivan, James Sullivan
you, Mr.
I got the street number wrong.
Who said that?
We finally met
Mr. Choi Kang
How did you know about me?
A person who manipulated the trial results
What should we do with these people?
I am being threatened
Isn't it your turn now?
One bomb
It will explode more
Take a good look
Sullivan's guys are pros
I'm dying
They say they're all blowing up
I guess Sullivan
What do you think you're going to do to the village?
What, do you have more than ten lives?
One of the bombs is
Wouldn't it be at the interview site?
If you interfere with my work in the future,
Then it doesn't end with a warning
- Ganga
- Don't come!
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri